Uh, bro
Hey, I really am
Is it okay to not go?
Even if my brother came,
All you have to do is take the contract with you.
They said they couldn’t do it
I'll sign right away, okay?
Okay, okay, call me
uh
Well, you cheated and your career was ruined.
Really?
He didn't seem like the kind of person who would cheat.
He was a very nice person.
This is naive, fall for it
Type ‘Seonwoohae Fraud Case’ on the portal.
No, man, kid.
Oh, that's right
Has the previously uploaded video been taken down?
I saw that
The baby didn't cry and was bitter.
Oh, I kinda like that too
It feels like I'm acting
Wow, isn't that creepy?
No, you don't even know
He ate his own mother
Let's stop with the past...
What are you doing to make it worse?
When it's time to be crazy
Take care of your food bowl
I can't even watch my actors or guards.
- Hey, this is really...
- Stop, stop, stop.
- Stop it, stop it.
- Let go.
Stop it! huh?
iced coffee!
Oh, what? ah!
Oh, what!
스폰 없었고
사기는 내 이름 판 새끼들이 쳤고
나도 그거 갚느라 뺑이 쳤고
우리 엄마 내가 잡아먹은 거
아주 잘 알고
어디다 손을 대, 이 *새끼가
나와
네가 여기 왜?
You said Mr. Geonno was coming.
You...
Did you hear everything, from the beginning?
After hearing everything, why...
Are you hearing that?
From now on, just ignore everything I say.
Don't waste your energy on useless things
For no reason?
How can that be for nothing?
Don't deal with them one by one
People talk whatever they want anyway
Rolling around in the mud together
What are you going to do?
I'm going to roll around
I was already rolling around a lot.
I'm going to roll around until I become a mush, why?
Ha... Ah, why do I feel like I'm the only one?
So what should I do then?
Well, should I even be happy?
Getting criticized that I shouldn't have to hear
Seeing a rough situation
The girl I like
Because of me...
how you lived
Because I saw it and I know it
Because you lived hard
I didn't want you to be insulted.
What's the fuss about now?
It's time for guests to arrive soon.
What happened?
explain
Dongjun grabbed Jeyeon by the collar.
At that time, Seon Woo-hae came in.
- Seonwoohae?
- Yes
These are really...
Seong Je-yeon
Dongjun Han, you...
I came here because of copyright.
Approved by the original author
You said you needed it
Was that your agent?
So the name...
I can't do that
yes
I borrowed that name
Did you know?
Seon Woo-hae is Jin Mu-young?
Will I still stand here?
It was your first time here, but it was a little messy, right?
Would you like to go to the representative’s office and talk?
Ah
I'll guide you this way...
sign
Do I have to do it today?
I'm not in the mood
Because I'm not in a hurry
Let's go first today
Are you going?
The name written on the contract
Correct it accurately and leave it
- Yes
- Meeting date
Put it back in as soon as possible
Just go away, I don't want to see you
Ha...
Good luck!
uh?
I'll go first
Come after work
Oh no
It takes my soul away
go
uh!
Are you okay?
Hey, are you okay?
It's okay
Please go
Are you okay?
Yeah
Huh? nosebleed
Kid...
You must have been hurt a lot earlier too, right?
I didn't just agree and stay quiet.
When did you say you were my brother?
Next time you see me, please tell me that
To my brother
Are you there yet?
Didn’t the CEO say anything more?
Let's talk as we go.
I have to reschedule the meeting date.
Hey, look!
I fell earlier...
Don't do it, really.
It's embarrassing, really.
Why?
what?
It looks like that's me, and so on
Can't you feel shame?
I was even grabbed by the collar
I'm still upset though
what are you saying to me
It's driving me crazy, really.
너 아까 재수 털렸어
For no reason?
That's right
why are you smiling
Why are you hugging me?
Natural, really?
Stay still
너 얼굴 팅팅 부은 게
저 멀리서도 다 보인다, 아유
Hold on to this
Stay still
아니야, 아니, 내가 할게
yes
너 미팅 언제 할래?
회사 불편하면은 다 맞출 테니까
- Be sure to sign it.
- 하지 말래도 할 거야
How much money do you have?
While doing it
Burn some sorrow
Are you really...
Oh, if you burn it
I'm riding with you too!
- uh? You, hey
-Why?
- 야, 손으로 하지 마
- Ah...
Kid...
- 아니야, 남았나 봐, 괜찮아
- Wait a minute, wait a minute.
응, 응, 자
uh
Don't treat people like gorillas!
Hey, but
Wouldn't a gorilla be calmer than you?
그새 놀리지?
Sorry, I couldn't bear it.
You, that...
People at work were just talking about it
You're not going to keep thinking about it and paying attention, right?
Well, when it goes on air
I thought people would talk like that.
I said I would see you when I was young
Getting scolded by my mom
I secretly watched TV
Huh?
Even people like me
There will be, definitely
넌 참
I feel like it’s the same, huh?
Carrying a heavy bag
If you don't hold back and attack you
you live neatly
That's right
I'm living a really neat life
The world is crooked
So you just do it like today
- What?
- Explain what is unfair
If you hit me, take revenge
Okay, let's try again.
Turn on the blinker
check side mirrors
uh
Uh, wait behind me.
- Uh, now.
- Now?
- Now, now?
- Now, now, now!
- Uh, hey, hey, hey, hey!
No, do you want to keep going straight like this?
I'm going to ride the highway like this, really!
You can join next time
No chance?
No, you said you registered for the academy too.
If you're going to do that, go to the academy and do it!
When it's time to play three jobs
Focus on driving, on driving
I can't concentrate because of you
Don't you think?
Where did you get hit in the face?
Are you taking out your anger on me today?
Hey
don't get your license
Something like you appears on the road
I can't watch it
What is it like me?
you teach me properly
Shouldn't we talk about it?
how much more than this am I
Teach me well? really!
Hey, hey, look in front, in front, hey, really
Huh? son
This...
Why do you keep coming?
You said I came home?
Ehe, indeed
You really are like Seokju.
Are you doing it?
Isn’t Seok-ju’s personality really strange?
Don’t be like that, Seokju is kind.
Maybe
- My old album
- Uh
No, it can't be
Hey, your old album
Dad has it all
how much is your mom
It seemed like you were serving Shinjudanji.
Dad now...
Pay cash on delivery or send by express
I'll send it to you quickly
Ah, this, hey, this...
I'll send it to you quickly, uh, here we go!
Ah, yes, it's here quickly.
Hahaha
Please give me 5,000 won
Are you free?
Is it a publisher or a publisher?
Didn't you say you would?
Uh, that...
One deadline is over
It's relatively free, yeah
That's not what I'm talking about
Oh, you really hit the nail on the head.
This is a photo album, ah...
uh
This is the album
I really just
Without a house or a house
Even when you're begging, huh?
Leave it to someone you trust
I will definitely come and visit you...
these pictures
Because these are times that will never come again
That's right
It's better to look for albums than to be a brat
Because it would have been cheap
Well, if Seok-ju bothers you again,
tell me
Dad just said, okay?
Well, just say goodbye
I'll give it to you, just
He's my sister's son
Just looking at it is all...
I'm going!
Yeah
You're not going to give me a flower... are you?
okay
Going
Where is Seong Je-yeon?
Must have a license
Should I pick it?
Stop by at a gas station on the way.
My brother told me to fill it up with gas and return it.
Ha...
I don't even get a fever anymore
Where do I return it?
Aren’t you cold?
Ah
sister
How long have you been here?
Why, why are you here?
From earlier
What is that...
When I return my car, I bring it here.
I don't know where this is
Who are you? This is Nuri’s house.
Yes? Ohh?
sister
Talk to us...
- Yeah, it's too dangerous here.
- W, here?
Go somewhere out of sight
Huh? No, where, where?
Will you keep it a secret?
Oh, that hair
Just get picked, just
I'm in love
Are you the oppa who wants to argue, Seonwoohae?
It's also a sexual mess
Because I didn't say anything
Should we just skip this too?
I'm a bit cautious about saying this.
Even though your grades are a mess, if you end up in a relationship,
Even the grades I just passed by
Aren’t you the type of person to fight?
I don't think you're careful at all.
But
Who are you really?
Oppa, you’re a hot girl.
Some... Ha!
Oh, bro, are you dating too?
Some...
I think it's a waste of money
I didn't think you would do that.
But you
Are you insulting my brother just now?
No, I think my brother is frugal.
I respect you so much
Oh, I...
Wait, this
Oh, well, it's no big deal.
This
Buy something delicious and eat it
thank you
If an adult gives you something
Say ‘Thank you’
I was told to get it, my brother.
Well done
Was lunch here okay?
yes
Ah, thank you
I will eat well
According to the contract, it ends this month.
You know your contract is expiring, right?
yes
I am
In the flower bed tended by the CEO
Does it suit you?
What's the problem?
I've been thinking about it for a long time
The CEO told me everything.
These good things
Please do a lot of good things for me
You told me everything
I think I was lacking a lot
Um...
It looks like you've been thinking a lot.
how
Are there any companies you talk to?
If you don't have it, should I find out?
Oh no
Just with words
thank you
yes
The next film
It's an awkward time to choose.
I guess I lost my energy reading the script for no reason.
No
Please say goodbye
I will
Ever since you were this young
Hug me when I cry
I took pictures while appeasing them.
more passionately than my children
There was a time when I was raised
I've had a hard time
yes
Representative too.
Oh my
Are you not Taryn?
Me, who...
What, don’t you remember me?
when i was in high school
How much did you take care of me
Ah, ah, maybe Hyebin?
huh!
Ah, I see it all like this
Do you use SNS?
me a while ago
I started the enzyme business.
Let's go somewhere and have some tea
I'm really sorry
Let's do it next time, I'll buy it
Oh, you're busy.
Well, you were in the past too
To the point where I can't do well in school
It was busy
no
My condition now...
Could you please let me go?
Oh my
Who rang?
It's not me
Hey, why are you being so embarrassing to people?
No...
Hey, that's enough, that's enough
Cover your face while pretending to wipe.
Are you going to cry more?
You can go over there
What else are you giving me?
coffee, cigarettes
handkerchief
It's really like this
Isn't it a task?
yes?
I just hope you have a good time on your way
No, over there...
Ha, I'm annoyed
Ha...
work?
I?
What, really?
What is this?
Oh, that's right, my bag, ha...
my bag
Can you please return it?
Why do you keep crying?
think about it
Can I at least tell you?
Why do you keep crying?
yes
here is my business card
Please tell me here
Huh, that's really weird
Ha, who is weirder?
Feel free to be weird
Why did you bother to chase me?
What you are saying is itself
Because it's really strange
our day
atmosphere on the rooftop
I don't think it was bad
‘We’?
'atmosphere'?
Please just be honest.
That way, I can also decide my attitude.
I left my bag and went to get it.
It's unfair because it's work.
no, that way
I'm not asking you to be honest!
About me
When the opposite sex approaches
I think it's all work.
I think it's selfish
Well, at first
Kindness, good will, whatever.
In the end, we all wanted the same thing.
What's different about that one?
I think you're feeling better
- That's good.
- Hey!
Are you kidding me?
I wasn't joking
Are you short?
Ha, you old man!
No, if I'm being honest, it's kind of cute.
Why do you keep pissing people off?
Not yet now
I feel like I'm dying!
Braided...
If I'm selfish
Does working make you feel less hot?
No, I hope I don't get upset
Were you going to call it selfless?
no, what
Why do you speak so strangely?
no, actually there isn't
If I had, I wouldn't do this either.
No, I mean
Why do I get less fever?
Why are you saying that?
Need less heat
Because we can only talk if you calm down
The idea was to calm down a bit.
Hey
you
If you like me, you'll die
Oh, what did I...
Why...
Uh, bro
- Brother
- Uh
Do you come here often?
Ah, hey
This
Please return your house to your home.
Put it somewhere out of sight
This is what I ask for.
Now
I faced him
He said pottery is his hobby.
Match?
Oh, hey, is it pretty?
The deal you made?
acid deal
Brother, please listen to my favor too.
I'll contact you soon
Hey, if it's related to mother-in-law
He doesn't come here often
That wasn't the request, though.
Going
Hello, Bebop!
hi beat
Pay me the taxi fare
Seokju went over there.
Ask her to give it to you
Huh? when?
ha
Is that true, Kim Seok-ju?
There was something with me?
Wake up from your dream!
I didn't want to know
you go and say
Hey, you need to pay for the taxi fare.
Oh, yes, just a moment.
Oppa, oppa!
What are you doing? quickly
Oh, really
You, huh? Come here and bring...
Yes, change is okay.
- Yes, thank you, yes.
- thank you
Ha...
Can you just eat something like this?
You said you had a diet.
Ah, filming is over, I’m unemployed these days.
But is the store usually this quiet?
While you're here, why don't you buy some?
You said you have a lot to do to buy flowers.
Seong Je-yeon
Ha, right
My senior bought a lot for me.
Why did I think everything was natural?
But did you talk about that with your senior?
I've been watching these days
I can't even contact you
Ah, this is what Seokju gave me.
The woman I met said she gave it to me, I'll give you more
Why are you telling me that?
I didn't do it because of you
Ha, it's increasing day by day during this time.
I thought it wasn't acting but intuition.
Match?
I don't know about acting
I've grown taller a lot, yeah
Now I get an award for my acting
Are you mocking me for not getting it?
What should I do, even taunting you?
Do you have a sense of victimization?
What do you know about retirement?
I've been acting for 10 more years
Hey, I debuted earlier.
This is for you, senior.
The words are always short and just
Unless you are a teacher
I'm so senior
what how
Would you please speak up, senior?
It's okay to treat me poorly
Buy some flowers, sir.
How can I not buy one, I really
This
Huh?
When Kim Seok-ju comes, give it back to me.
Huh? Yeah
What?
What how, I
Should I just say I don't like it?
Oh, I don't know
Ah, I don’t know, me too, ah!
I'm so confused today, brother.
Can't you go?
Sincerely
Okay, I'll go.
Lend me 50,000 won
Ha...
Ah, why are you looking like that?
I'm not asking for it, I'm asking for it to be borrowed
Welcome
- Oh, that one.
- Squid
- Thank you, sell a lot.
- Yes, come again next time.
How much is this, boss?
It's 10,000 won for four.
It's saltier
Hey, drink water, drink water
Hey, well, you...
Don't overdo it today
You did a lot of difficult tests.
yes, i understand
thank you
Have a hard time
I think I'll miss it anyway
Here it is
Wow
Got it
It's here
- thank you
- Yes
I should say thank you
Do you want to eat this?
Can I eat it?
hmm!
It's pink, show me your teeth
Yes, this
There is
sweet
Turn right
Watch out for the glass, glass
Oh, I've got my hands, my hands, oh, wait...
Okay, okay, really.
Hey, what did you buy...
-Sleep, wait a minute.
-Why?
Did you hear anything outside?
What are you talking about?
Your father passed by earlier...
Ah, back, back, back, hide back
Over there, over there, quickly
Hey, sit down, sit down
Shh, hush, quiet
Did you go? Okay, hey, move on.
let's go
Don't make a sound, stay still...
Hey, quick, quick.
Wow
ah!
huh?
Why is this here...
What are you doing in your room?
Yeah
Oh, what a surprise.
Are you here now?
You decided to have breakfast today.
I'm so hungry
Then let me just do this quickly
I'll hide and go out, stay out for a while
Yeah, hide it well and come out
uh
I was surprised
Mom, have you finished work now?
you really grasp the information
Just properly...
Oh, what company?
Are you making the representative stay up all night?
Ah, hey, hey, hand, hand
Just eat and take a sauna.
Really!
You will never see a delivery address again
If you enter it incorrectly...
I love you, bro
But why did we hide?
Then what
Should I go and say hello boldly, huh?
- Stay still.
- Let's just stay.
But what were you hiding earlier?
Ah, an old album
Ah...
I'm afraid I'll feel bad when I see my sister...
I feel good enough
'Cause I'm in a bad state, all the time
Because I don’t like my mom
My mom's name is
It was Muyoung, right? Jin Muyoung?
Ah...
At that time, in that corner of the country
Even if I didn’t go to the location
There was no fate with you
We have such an old story
Are you just going to do it?
'membrane'?
You clean up the girl
The story of throwing away a child
I haven't done it yet
older sister
Starting from the morning breeze, the words are a bit harsh.
Sister, if you say that
I'm really sad
It was all a matter of time.
Oh, it's from the past?
The wrapping paper looks decent.
Why didn't you wait for me then?
Did you like your mom that much?
older sister
Sister, at that time, without saying a word,
After going to Seoul
I had a really hard time too
All my life, I've been waiting for my sister
Stuck on that beach
You couldn't live there
You came back, finally to your sister.
You came back when you were unhappy.
What are you coming back for?
After that happens, mom
You didn't come!
Wow, really
Sister, you really talk too much.
Sister, that was just sad.
I needed comfort
You are not that kind of person.
What am I to you?
What kind of being am I?
Do you love me?
I live like this because I love you
Why do I like you?
I don't know sometimes
Sister still to me
Emotions come first
You're just screaming
If you're with me
Do you remember when you were young?
when it was hot
My sister is still at that time
I couldn't escape
I'll be out for a while
Aren't you coming here?
Hey, Seonwoo-chan!
I'll move it too
Go in
Uh, that...
I didn't come because you wanted to come.
What did I order you to do?
That's what I came to do for you.
To make my mom feel bad
I didn't call you
Have you eaten?
- What about Mom?
- Let's go, I made a reservation for breakfast.
Ah...
Oh, where did you really put it, where on earth did you put it?
Uh, it's mom.
Oh my, really
What's good about this guy?
Why aren't you looking ahead?
- Hello
- Oh, hello.
Me, this
I still have some left today
You're doing this again
I'm really fine
Last time, the price of ice cream was also
You didn't receive it.
Ah...
If you keep doing this
I won't get it next time either.
Ah...
Because they will soon wither
You can take it with peace of mind.
Brother!
uh
I'll see you then, have a good time.
Ha...
Are you very shy?
When are you going to confess?
I don't know?
Because if you just give it to me, it will be noticeable
You're passing it around to everyone around you.
It's not my taste
- Ouch
- Just throw away the remaining flowers.
Isn’t it annoying every time?
They give it out for free every time.
I'm coming to buy some.
And brother, do that shit
A hundred hairs are torn off
You can bet
Yeah, yeah
Because I think love does it
I'm pissed, really.
Pull out all your hair
Are you in love? With whom?
- boy friend?
- No
Just why
Someday love?
Ha, sheesh
I'm definitely going to have to have it someday
Our world
- I'm popular.
- Oh, really?
Oppa, it's really because you don't know.
In other words, cancel it quickly.
Hey, you didn't say you were coming today.
Huh?
No, how do you know my house...
Excuse me
What is it?
No, what happened, all of a sudden
Ah, this is
Since it's my first time coming to your house, I'm writing this
- Huh?
- and
This will come later
Jujeonburi to eat at Happyeong
Because the test taker is going to eat it
With good ingredients
Why didn't I think of this?
Because I'll think about it
You really are, huh?
Take care of these things delicately
Contrary to what it seems
I guess it's nature
Ah!
Oh, I didn't bring coffee.
Even if I don’t have coffee, I
I'm about to get off, wait a minute
Chi
Anyone can see that the two of them had a child.
I think you raised it.
Ah, it's hot!
Hey, are you okay?
It's not hot
Huh?
Why didn't this boil?
Hey, the code is missing.
Why didn't it stick?
Are you stupid?
you
-You go.
- Huh?
Because you are at home
I'm nervous, you go home
Go, go
Go, quickly
What is it, cute
Oh my, what can I say?
Uh, this book
Where did you get it?
I had a really hard time finding it.
It's been out of print for a long time.
- Ah...
- That...
sign
Can you do it?
sine...
yes
Here
Wow!
Wow, awesome
Ah, the debut novel
How did you come to apply?
I'm eating ramen
In a book written with a pot holder
Well, there was an advertisement for a contest.
They said they would give me a prize if I was elected.
I sent the manuscript and it's done.
- You're a little annoying, you.
- What?
The first time you wrote it all at once?
Are you not doing the spring literary contest?
I didn't know there was such a thing, in the first place
I wanted to become a novelist
Because it wasn't
You're so annoying, you
Oh, really
But
How old are you two?
Have you been dating?
Was that too rude?
Just because it looks good...
We just...
Yes, my friend.
When you hear something like that
In such a situation where I feel like I'm getting skinny
- Oh...
- Just friends
Oh!
Oh, that's right
Ugh, chicken skin is growing.
hello there
To PD
Please give me my regards.
Yes, thank you, bye.
goodbye
Ah
PD To my daughter
I came here to get my face stamped.
Well, let's do it together
Ugh
I'll go and see
I have to return to work
Shall I take you there?
Do you feel good?
I?
How does it feel to meet a fan?
It seems like it just popped up, right now?
Half is right and half is...
Ha...
Where shall I take you?
To the ends of the earth?
This is
Is it right to take you there?
Um...
It's a bit inappropriate
people tell you
I guess it wasn't just harsh.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about student Eunji Yoo.
I just
I wrote it to chase money.
It gained meaning thanks to that friend.
Hey, but
How did he get it?
- Oh, your first novel?
- Yes
Hey, about that.
What is ‘Beloved Gorilla’, what is the title?
Anyway, whatever
'The world is a bit
‘I want it to be beautiful’?
Well...
Do you want the world to be beautiful?
who? you?
you
The author said that
I said that?
No, well, all three books were the same.
Where did you copy it?
I don't know, I guess it was like that back then, whatever.
I don't remember
Hey
Just do it for me
I don't have to have anyone next to me, so I take it.
Come back well
I'll go from here
Even if you think
Inefficient, isn't this picture?
They say he's coming back
I can't ask you to play
I don't want to send it away
Jeyeon noona!
uh? oh my!
Oh my, Mr. Sang-yeop
But what is your name noona?
Rather than calling you team leader
It's better to call me sister.
Still, people
Because it can be misunderstood
There's no harm in being careful.
Are you mistaken?
So who is this person?
It looked like your sister was getting out of the car.
No way
lover?
No, no, no
Well, it's not like that.
Just...
Chu, performer
Ah, these days with Taerin.
Appearing on TV together
Hello, my name is Lee Sang-yeop.
Sorry for the misunderstanding
yes and no
But sister, did you change your hair?
uh?
Oh no, my head...
Isn’t it really pretty?
Uh, huh?
hmm!
Let's go see the performer.
- Goodbye...
- Come in.
Are you on your way to work?
Yes, because I'm going to the military.
Call the manager
I have to decide on a time.
I see.
If a warrant comes out
Hurry up and go to the military
duty of national defense
You don't have to do it all
Drive a stake in
CEO
I...
Author of ‘A World Made of Ashes’
We are coordinating the meeting date
I have to see that shave again.
I understand
I'll give you a vacation for a while, so take a break.
Words are vacations, you know what I mean?
Han Dong-jun is also on probation, starting from today.
Caused a commotion at the company
sorry
Apart from my housemaster
The officials lowered the lifeline.
Well done on that one.
I got hit first
6 years
Vacation after 6 years, no
Suspension?
Um...
It lasts a long time
Hello!
Starting today, I went to work for the first time.
This is Choi Gippeum!
I am the only person
There's no need to be so loud
Yep!
The chair hasn't been delivered yet
roughly over there
Sit down with the unopened box
It's me standing there with style
Because I'm not doing this
Ah, Taerin will do well.
I'm sure this line will be well received.
I'm done
What should we do now?
Um...
Ah, the newbie has no clue.
Oh, would you like to buy some coffee?
very good idea
Mr. Joy, I also want to eat
If you have it, buy it together.
yes
Also buy a power strip
head!
No wandering thoughts!
I don’t want to think about anything else either!
concentration, focus
Last!
head!
Ha...
What is it?
Why are you here?
I don't know
After
fish oil
How far can I see?
well
I
As far as you want
Chi
- Thank you for your hard work!
- Thank you for your effort!
Ah, thank you for your hard work!
Ah...
please
Who snores during meditation?
Didn't I say anything weird?
You didn’t talk in your sleep, did you?
you can stop now
How many times this week?
Because of you, I used up all my kendo gym passes.
Really...
Do you think about it because you are free?
Yes, I will enrich it for you.
thank you, yes
yes
hello
Why do you look at me like that?
I feel like I see you often
Did you do that?
It seems like the flower pots change often?
Ah
If the flower pot stays in one place for a long time
People think it's not selling
how do you know that
What, do you also do mind reading?
Then read my mind too
- Why me?
- Right.
What is it?
What did you do when you were suspended?
uh?
No, the vice principal at that time
You were suspended from school.
Can't go to school for a week
Ah
But why are you talking about that now?
What are you bragging about?
I ate something similar
I made money
More construction work going on
I also work on loading and unloading parcels.
Ah, there
It makes the rice cake really delicious.
There was
I don't know if it's still there
Is this the store you often went to back then?
Not often
What do you eat?
Because time to sleep is decreasing
I finished my part-time job that day too.
I'm trying to fall asleep
Then it's like I can't wake up.
It's my first day at school after transferring.
I stayed up all night
I took a bus
I fell asleep on the bus
Did you continue to sleep after that?
Have you been watching me sleep?
Because I am the class president
No, I lead by example.
How annoying it must have been
Chi
I have to work
Are you going to keep talking to me? huh?
What do you do after you finish?
Geonno’s part-time job
What do you do when it's over?
I should go home and sleep
I see.
I guess being suspended from school was a huge shock.
Did the taste go away?
I know
Why am I here doing this?
Why do you look at me like that?
How do I see it?
Ah...
It's too much to leave the car, really.
Seong Je-yeon, you got punished for doing that, right?
You're getting your punishment now, man.
Huh? Yes, Director.
Tell me, what is it?
I hired a new employee, what should I ask them to do?
Uh, company rules, written forms.
vehicle operation
Well, I need to tell you something like this.
What is your experience, how many years do you have?
personal history? I don't have it
It's been a while since I returned home.
Did you graduate?
No, we hire experienced workers first...
Boss, a bouquet of flowers.
Please
What's going on?
I didn't buy it even once
A special shooter to me
I changed companies
Looks like it needs a visit
To create an atmosphere?
Man or woman?
Why do you ask that?
How long does it take?
Go straight from here?
Are you sad that you’re leaving?
We ask all our customers the same thing.
Would you like to write a message card, sir?
Girl, it takes 30 minutes, I'll go right away, I don't use it
Ah...
It wasn't like me
Okay, see you that day, tax accountant.
Please go in
Are you Hannah Bang?
Here
Whatever it is, congratulations
give me my money
It's your first time buying a bouquet of flowers.
Oh my
Where are you? Are you here?
Oh, that looks really cool.
What is it, Motaerin?
Why are you here?
Hello, senior
I deliberately stole it
This!
Oh my, you traitors!
Ha...
Is it belief or faith?
Say such cool things
He left
What about the newbie manual I requested?
I sent it by email
my manual is real
You know I won't give it to anyone, right?
Thanks to you, I survived, thank you
Now, ‘The New Utopia’
How do you feel as your first customer?
At what point?
You said that before
Rather than a company where you have to work
The company you want to work for
The intention is to make
Ah, that...
The mission is a bit weird, but...
I never thought it was strange
It seems a bit like a religious group?
- Hehe, big.
- 'Hehe, big'?
‘Hehe, big’? ‘Hehe, big’?
We should have discussed this
What if a company like this was going to come? uh?
What kind of company is this?
Oh, that's right
Taerin
read it
If you like it
I will do business somehow
‘Kongjwi Patjwi’?
Ah, I barely managed to bring it to modern times.
Let's spend the Joseon Dynasty
I wonder if the company will be okay!
It's a modern investigation.
Why have you become so careless when you haven't seen it?
Snack delivery has arrived
- Oh, that's him...
- celebrity
Wow, he’s a celebrity.
hello
Greetings, this is our actor Tae-rin Mot.
My former co-worker Seong Je-yeon
hello
If you come, run away.
Do you really need to become a manager?
What are you talking about?
To the world-renowned University of Hong Kong
This is Choi Gippeum
A place that will put you to work right away
This was the only place
Here
Driving rather than academic background
This is a place where it is rated higher.
It's a shame
I will help you
- Ugh!
- Fish oil!
Why is this here?
It suits me to be there
I feel like I should be there
Maybe they don’t know how to throw it away!
Oh, I reported it and put a sticker on it.
If you give it to me, I will take it.
That...
Should we also look into cleaning companies?
oh!
From the building management office
I have to ask.
Okay then, Mr. Joy.
I got something to do
I'm going to the management office.
- Come back.
- Yes
I'll remember when I was a new senior.
Hey, I was much faster.
A
I added a few more songs
Please tell me to find a lot
Did he send it because he was doing business?
Hannah Bang sent flowers.
Director
At that time, Taerin sent it on the radio.
the flower delivery
Maybe
Did you know about that store and send it to me?
What store? I don't know, why?
What a fate is
Isn’t it ironic?
Why do I feel like I'm really being punished?
If it was originally the same
What are you, a bee target?
I would have robbed it
senior
Who are you talking to?
Am I a little scared?
therefore
I couldn't refute it
Why does he make me feel uncomfortable?
I said she wasn't here, but the fairy sister
Oh, there's nothing...
Oh, don't do it, I'm really scared!
and
I told that fairy sister
Did I tell you not to give me money?
Everything is wrong.
Then I'll be here
Hey, are you okay?
Look look
Are you hurt?
Uh, it's okay
I'm glad it didn't break
I'm sorry, bro.
No, it's okay, it's okay
eight, nine, hundred
One, two, three, three
I've been forgetting it for so long
This is what happens when you like someone
How does it disappear into blackness?
What, poetic license?
hello
Ah!
Ah...
I feel like I'm screwed
happy birthday, mom
I'm going to see my mom tomorrow
Can I talk about you?
Hey, why are you asking that?
I can tell you
What are you going to say?
Won't you tell me?
mom
Mom too
I think he'll like it
Yeah
Did you have any related symptoms?
I don't feel particularly energetic
I can't feel anything
Medicines to be taken together
I'm going to prescribe a new prescription for you.
This is not covered...
Am I going to die?
Amyloidosis
It's a very difficult and tricky disease.
There are not many cases in Korea.
When do you die?
Well, in layman’s terms.
Maybe tomorrow
What may happen in 10 years
I know you're suffering
if i
Me when I was nineteen
There's a chance to meet you, right?
Then
my life in the future
I think it will be a huge spoiler
‘Play when you can’
‘Where should you invest?’
‘Avoid the day you get slapped’
What about you?
me?
Well...
Should I buy you a meal?
Hey, then I'm too
It seems secular.
You should quickly spoil it for her too.
Um...
‘Life anyway’
‘It’s like a bet’
Oh!
The introduction is good
Good...
I don't know what happens next
What will your child think when he hears this?
Try something like this, squeeze it out a little bit
'Because it's a bet'
‘There are days when we pick too much’
‘I wonder if this is okay’
‘There will be days when you lose everything’
Delivery to Room 505, Building 102 has arrived.
Uh...
Ah, I like this.
- thank you
- Thank you, goodbye.
'You probably'
'Losing a lot'
'Most days I get a little bit'
‘But you are’
'I'm not betting on bad luck'
'I know'
'If it were you'
- What?
- eww!
huh?
Uh, to your mom.
What did you say about me?
Did you swear?
uh?
That...
Are you curious why you came?
Yeah
Are you excited?
Are you looking forward to it? I'm looking forward to it
Ah...
me
I like you
Ah...
At this timing?
Kid!
Maybe I
Is it too late?
Ha...
I guess I'm crazy
I shouldn't feel good
the world
It's kinda beautiful
Let’s turn it around
Just think about your senior
I have to set the mood first.
What are you going to do?
It's because I have a plan
What did you want to become, Mo Taerin?
Hae published a book?
I...
They say I'm dying
If something like this happens again
It will end like this anyway
Why are you doing this to me?
We should stop watching
To you, I
Just...
That's about it.